有喷泉
Oh, a fountain.
我爱喷泉
I love fountains.
我们裸奔吧
Let's skinny-dip!
不是吧  亲爱的
Come on, baby.
来啊  很好玩的
Come on. It'll be fun.
现在  你开玩笑的吧
Now? Are you kidding?
如果你抓到我  我就是你的了
If you catch me, You can have me.
那好  我来了
Okay, I'm coming.
来了  我过来喽
I'm coming! I'm coming over.
裤子脱了
Take your pants off!
-到这边来  -我来了
- Get over here! - I'm coming.
我发誓  杰斯敏
I swear, Jasmine.
你会有报应的
This has always been The way with you.
你这一生不可能永远得寸进尺
You can't just go through life Asking for an egg in your beer
妄想别人还你两次钱
And your money back twice.
还你两次钱
Your money back towice
抱歉  "妈妈  如果我这么令你失望
Sorry. "Oh, mama, if I'm such a disappointment to you,
我不知你为何还要回家
"I don't know why you even Bother coming home.
不是吗  奶奶"
Isn't that right, granny?"
"你们俩都闭嘴  我要看故事书了"
"Shut up, both of you. I'm tryin' to watch my stories."
"真希望我没离开巴黎  还有戏剧"
Oh,  I wish I'd never left paris. And scene.
很好  我们从头再来一遍
Good. Good. All right, let's take it from the top.
你们俩别这样
Oh, guys, come on.
难道不想让我得到这个角色吗
Don't you want me to land this role?
当然想
Of course we do. It's--
听着  我们谈的可是一部百老汇话剧的主角
Look, we are talking about The lead in a broadway play.
这是潜在的金矿
This is A potential gold mine.
如果火了  谁知道会演多久
If it's a hit, who knows how long it could run?
那样我就可以一直巡演
Then I could take it on the road.
你是指离开我们
You mean you'd leave us?
一年只演九个月
Well, only for nine months of the year.
宝贝别伤心  你也别暗自高兴
Oh, don't look so sad. And you, don't look so happy.
卡塞尔
Castle.
我马上到  好的
I'll be right there. All right.
死亡  谋杀和伤害都凑齐了
Death, murder, mayhem-- Whole enchilada.
抱歉不能陪你排练了
Sorry to bail on rehearsal.
别担心  阿丽克西斯可以顺便读了你那部分
Oh, don't worry. Alexis can read both parts.
她上午不去上学没事的  对吧
It's all right if she misses A morning of school, isn't it?
-带上我  -去犯罪现场吗
- Take me with you. - To a crime scene?
会有教育意义的  求你了
It'd be educational. Please.
自己找藏身之所吧
Find your own hiding place.
白人  女性
Caucasian female.
一对裸跑情人尽早发现她的
Couple of skinny-dippers found her this morning.
那可真是大煞风景
Bet that killed the mood.
没有钱包  无身份证
Purse is missing, no i.d. And get this--
我们没找到她的鞋
We couldn't find her shoes.
我猜还在舞会的白马王子手中[灰姑娘]
I'm gonna go with "still with prince charming at the ball."
需要找南瓜车和小老鼠吗
Should we look for a pumpkin and some mice?
我猜不用了
Ah, I guess not.
彻查一下广场四周的建筑
Canvass the buildings Surrounding the plaza
让军装警察查查垃圾箱  看有没有她的包
And get uniforms to check trash cans and dumpsters for her purse.
好的
Aye-aye.
-早上好  蕾妮  -早上好
- Hi, Lanie. - Hey.
-死因  -利器刺死
- Cause of death? - Stabbing.
致命伤在背部
There's a fatal wound  In her back.
-也许是抢劫杀人  -有可能
- Maybe a robbery gone wrong? - Maybe.
要查出她的身份
We gta find out who she is
这么晚了出现在这里做什么
And what she was doing here so late,
她身材高挑  美丽动人
Well, she's tall, she's gorgeous,
比标准体重轻10磅  烫过头发
10 pounds underweight, her hair is fried
眼妆很浓
And she's wearing too much eye makeup.
她是个模特  也就是说昨晚
She's a model, which means she was probably
她可能在一个俱乐部  毕竟是时尚周
At a club last night. It is, after all, fashion week--
当世界上的辣妹
When all the hottest women in the world
突降一些时尚夜总会  比如蝗虫
Descend upon the hippest night spots like locusts.
不过真的蝗虫是吃东西的
Only locusts eat.
你告诉我杀手是谁吗
Can you tell me who killed her?
-那闭嘴  -这是她手腕上的
- Then pipe down. - This was on her wrist.
她昨晚去了一家俱乐部
She was at a club.
是泰迪·法罗的商标
That's Teddy Farrow's logo.
此人设计女士服装  高端昂贵的那种
He designs clothes for women-- Upscale, expensive.
我的信用卡和我看到泰迪的东西都很心痛
Oh, my credit card and I are painfully aware of Teddy's designs.
上次离婚后  我几乎请求禁止生产这个
I almost asked for custody of them after my last divorce.
她的裙子上有标签吗
Is there a label in her dress?
泰迪·法罗系列
Teddy Farrow collection.
如果她是泰迪的模特
Well, if she is one of his models,
或许他能认出她  谢了蕾妮
Maybe he can identify her for us. Thank you, Lanie.
不客气
You're welcome.
我的下一本新书有思路了
I can already see the blur by next book jacket.
那是在一次纽约时装周
"It's fashion week  In new york city,
对时装的热情是死也值得
And the clothes Are to die for."
各位  最后五分钟
Five minutes, people.
是詹娜  全名为詹娜·麦博伊德
That's Jenna. Jenna Mcboyd.
她今天本应为我走秀的
She was supposed to walk for me today.
天啊  怎么回事
My god. What happened.
今天凌晨时候被人刺伤致死
She was stabbed some time this morning.
真难以置信
I can't believe it.
我昨晚还在派对上看到她
I mean, I saw her last night at my party.
你注意到派对上有什么不正常吗
Did you notice anything unusual at the party?
她很焦虑  但这些天她都这样
She was agitated, but that wasn't so unusual for her these days.
-哪个  -好的
- Which one? - Okay.
-知道原因吗  -她最近压力很大
- Any idea what was wrong? - Yeah, she was stressed out.
别用粉色的腰带  用蓝色的
Hey, not the pink sash. The blue one.
-对不起  -詹娜来自小镇
- Sorry, sir. - Look, Jenna was a small-town girl.
坐汽车从俄亥俄州来
Straight off the bus from Ohio.
你是指她很单纯
You're saying  She was an innocent.
她是颗冉冉升起的新星
She was a rising star,
但她还没准备好
But she wasn't ready for what was coming her way.
什么意思
What do you mean?
各位  最后四分钟
Four minutes, people. Four minutes.
我是指  我想让她成为这一季
I mean... I was thinking of making her
广告大片的女主角
The face of my campaign.
意味着硬照  杂志
That would've meant photo shoots, magazines,
时代广场的广告牌  《旅行周刊》
Billboards in Times Square, Travel,
更不用提大笔的收入
Not to mention a very generous paycheck.
对一个天真的女孩来说  这些挺不错的
Seems to be all pret heady stuff for a naive young girl.
最近几周她很情绪化  有点多疑
In recent weeks, she'd become so bad tempered, uh, paranoid.
我开始怀疑在重要广告大片上
I'd started to wonder if she wasn't too inexperienced
她是否经验过少
For a major campaign.
你说她有点多疑
You said that she was paranoid.
-有没有可能是吸毒了  -她不会
- Any chance She was doing drugs? - Not her style.
泰迪  如果你想让我拍那些女孩
Teddy, if you want me to shoot the girls,
先把装腔作势的乐队小子从我位子上赶走
You need to get that boy-band poser out of my seat.
怀亚特  我会处理的
Wyatt, I'll take care of it.
法罗先生  还有几个问题就好
Uh, Mr. Farrow, just a couple more questions.
可以  请快点
Yes. But quickly, please.
昨晚的派对上  詹娜跟谁一起的
Who was Jenna with last night at your party?
卡塞尔  专心点
Castle, focus.
我只看到了她一会儿
I only saw her briefly.
她基本都和她的死党  塞拉一起
She spent most of her time with Sierra, her best friend.
塞拉就在那里  穿婚纱的那个
That's Sierra there, with the wedding gown.
如果没有问题了
So if that's all,
我得去处理最后一些细节了
Now I really must take care of last-minute details.
最后一个问题
Uh, one last thing.
詹娜离开派对的时候  她是穿着鞋的吗
When, uh, Jenna left your party, was she wearing shoes?
克里斯提·鲁布托[招牌红底鞋]的
Yes. Uh, Christian Louboutin
桃色缎面红底鞋
Pink satin pumps
借给她参加派对穿的
I lent her for the evening.
她的礼服可是独一无二的一件
The dress she was wearing was a one of a kind.
希望你们能还给我
I don't suppose We can have it returned.
现在是证据
It's in evidence now.
而且礼服背面  她被刺的位置有个洞
And it has a hole in the back of it where she was stabbed.
抱歉
Sorry.
里克·卡塞尔  今天碰到你真有趣
Rick Castle. It's so funny  I ran into you today.
我刚在来的路上买了这个
I just bought this on my way in.
看啊  封面是我
Oh, look at that.  It's my cover.
杂志已经上架了
And it's on stands already.
理查德·卡塞尔最新小说引来希特热浪
"Richard Castle gets the inspiration for his latest novel, 'Heat wave'..."
他小说的新主人公是妮基·希特
"And his new character Nikki Heat
灵感来自一位优秀的纽约警察
From new york's finest."
很不错的吧
That's nice, right?
-你能  -当然  你的名字是
- Could you-- - Yes, absolutely. Who should I make it out to?
你不记得我了
Oh. You don't remember me?
我当然记得  你是
No--yes. Of course I do. Yeah. You're--
莉娜
Rina.
就是莉娜  我在那个派对上遇到你
Rina. Yes. We met At that party with that--
当时很晚了  真疯狂
That thing that was late, And it was crazy.
那夜真美好
That--wow, what a night.
上场了  模特们  各就各位
Let's go, models. Take your places.
都过来  站成一排
I need you up here and in line.
给你电话
Here.
打给我
Call me.
你也在上面的
You're in here, too, you know?
天啊
Oh, god.
我很不自在
I feel sick.
这件婚纱本来是她穿的
And I'm wearing her gown.
她才是压轴出场的  而非我
She was supposed to close the show today, not me.
我今早给她打了无数个电话
I called her this morning like a million times,
但都转到了语音信箱
But it just kept going to voice mail.
詹娜是几点离开派对的
When did Jenna leave the party
大概午夜
Uh, around midnight.
我以为她回家了
I assumed she was going home.
法罗先生提到她最近很烦躁
Mr. Farrow mentioned that She seemed agitated lately.
明天泰迪就要宣布新一季的代言人了
Tomorrow, Teddy' s announcing The new face of his collection.
詹娜够格  但她有点紧张
Jenna was up for the job, and she was a little tense.
-但她没理由紧张  -为什么
- But she didn't have any reason to be. - Why not?
已经定下就是她了  詹娜是泰迪的最爱
She was a lock. Jenna was Teddy' s favorite.
天啊
Oh, god.
特拉维斯知道吗
Does travis know?
她的丈夫  他会崩溃的
Her husband? He's gonna be devastated.
他们非常相爱
They were so in love.
我11点睡的觉
I went to bed around 11:00.
我想她回家后会叫醒我
I figured she'd wake me when she got in.
但凌晨3点  她还没回来
But at 3:00 a.m., She wasn't home.
所以我打了她电话
So...  I called her cell phone.
没人接
She wasn't there.
我随即报了警
I called the cops.
他们说我要等48小时
They said I had to wait 48 hours
才能报失踪
Till I could Report her missing.
我说  你们不了解我妻子
I told them, "You don't know my wife.
这么晚她都没回来  一定是出事了
If she's not home by now, something happened to her."
天啊  我应该去那儿的
God, I should've been there.
那些派对  他们
These parties, you know, they're just--
每个人都那么虚伪
Everyone's so phony.
特拉维斯  我懂这很困难
Travis, I know this is difficult,
但这个问题我还是得问
But I have to ask you this question.
你想想有谁
Was there anyone that you can think of
会伤害詹娜
That would want to do harm to Jenna?
你是在说笑吗
You're kidding, right?
我们报案了
We--we--we filed the reports.
其他警察还没交给你们吗
Did--didn't the other cops send 'em to yoguys?
-报案  -她被人骚扰
- Reports? - For harassment.
有人一直给詹娜寄信
Some guy was sending Jenna letters.
写一堆恶心的话
Like, writing all sorts of sick things.
还偷拍她
He was taking pictures of her, too.
好像一直在跟踪我们
It's like was watching us all the time.
她被吓坏了  我们俩都被吓坏了
She was falling apart. I mean, we both were.
我们差点就要搬走了
Hell, We almost moved back home.
你们报案了是吗
And you filed a report?
对  报了好几次
Yeah, a dozen of 'em.
而你们这些人  每次都说同样的话
And every time, you people said the same damn thing.
这里是纽约
That this is new york,
你们有更重要的事去做
And you got more important things to do
没空去查什么疯狂粉丝
Than to track down some annoying fan.
那她现在死了
And now she's dead.
我的妻子  死了
My wife... Is dead.
信是从苏豪区邮局寄出的
Letters were mailed from the soho post office.
没回信地址  没签名
No return address, no signature.
那个匿名跟踪者没写
So the anonymous stalker didn't
自己的名字和电话号码
Write down his name and number?
正如我所说
Yeah, I'm just sayin'.
今天我在地铁上看到你了  你看到我了吗
"I saw you today in the subway. Did you see me?
-我真想吃掉你  -这些够恶心了
- I wanted to taste you." - That's pretty sick stuff.
但因为他没直接威胁他们
But he doesn't make any direct threats.
所以詹娜和特拉维斯没能
That's why Jenna and Travis couldn't
得到那些同事的认真对待
Get the beat cops to take 'em seriously.
一对年轻人从小城镇来到大城市
Boy, two small town kids go to the big city
来实现梦想  而最终结果如斯
To follow their dreams, and then this.
我确定  这绝不是他们想要的童话结局
Not the fairy-tale ending they were looking for, I'm sure.
为了拍这些照片  他一定去过
You know, to take these shots, he would've had to have been
公寓附近的天台
On a rooftop pretty close to the apartment.
难怪她会被吓坏
No wonder she was freaked out.
查出天台的位置  看是否有线索
Find the roof, see if there's anything up there
能找出凶手
That we can use to identify him.
那些同事让詹娜失望了  我们绝不再犯
Those cops let Jenna down once. We're not gonna do it again.
灵书妙探  第二季
第三集
大家好  我回来了  买了炒粉
Hello. I'm home. And I brought chow fun.
-爸爸  晚上好  -晚上好
- Hey dad. - Hey
很好
Oh, nice.
但我在回家路上已经买过一本了
But I already picked up a copy on my way home.
你看了吗  她是不是人很好
Well, did you read it? Was she kind?
那作者喜欢你  也喜欢贝克特探长
The writer loved you. She loved detective Beckett.
她还很喜欢那书  基本上就是吹捧您
She even loved the book. It was your basic puff piece.
我确定你奶奶一定会有话说
Well, I'm sure my mother will find something to say
才不会让我得意
That will keep me from getting too puffed.
今晚不行
Not tonight she won't.
她在自己房间哀悼她事业的消亡
She's in her room, mourning the death of her career.
那部剧没要她吗
Oh, she didn't get that play?
要了  不过没给她想要的角色
She did. Just not the part she wanted.
制片人说她不适合演主角
The producer said she's not right to play the lead.
他们想要她演疯狂老奶奶
They want her to play the crazy granny.
疯狂老奶奶
Oh, the crazy granny.
而且在第一幕就死了
Who dies in act one...
还是在台下
Offstage.
不
No.
等电话
You expecting a call?
事实上  等回电话
A callback, actually.
我在时装周遇到了位年轻女士
I met a nice young woman at fashion week.
一小时前  我给她留了言
I left her a message about an hour ago.
模特
A model?
天  老爸  工作时还不忘美女
Gee, dad. Picking up hotties while you're working a case?
事实上是她先找上我的
She picked me up, as a matter of fact.
她说我们在别的地方见过
She said we knew each other from... Somewhere.
这是个咒语  无法抗拒
It's a curse, being so irresistible.
这次的美女叫什么  萝拉
What's this one's name-- Lola,
布瑞  塔蒂阿娜
Bree, Tatiana?
莉娜
Rina.
-你说莉娜吗  -是
- Did you say Rina? - Yeah.
-金发  -对
- Blonde hair? - Yeah.
-一双美丽的大眼睛  -对
- Bambi eyes? - Yeah.
-有点龅牙但很可爱  -对
- Cute little overbite? - Yeah.
爸爸  你认识莉娜的
Dad, you know Rina.
-她以前是我的保姆  -她以前什么
- She used to babysit me. - She used to what you?
保  姆
Baby... Sit.
记得吗  我们一起看《歌舞青春》
Remember? We watched "high school musical" together,
看了好多回
Like, a million times.
我隐约记得  她瘦瘦高高
I-I vaguely remember a-a-- Like, a gangly girl
脏脏的头发  戴牙套  叫卡特莉娜
With stringy hair and braces named katrina.
就是她
That's the one.
她就是那只变成天鹅的丑小鸭
She did the whole "ugly duckling to swan" thing,
改了名字  当了模特
Shortened her name and became a model.
你能遇到她真是太有趣了
That's so funny that you ran into her.
世界太小了
The world is really small.
对  小而残酷
Yeah, small and cruel.
据推断死亡时间
I'm putting the time of death
是凌晨2点到5点
Between 2:00 and 5:00 a.m.
她半夜12点离开派对
She left the party at midnight.
那之后两小时她在哪里
So where was she for two hours?
有被性侵吗
Any signs of sexual assault?
没  但有打斗的痕迹
No, but she put up a fight.
死者手臂和手部有淤青
There's some bruising on her arms and hands,
裙子被扯破
Her dress was torn.
她脸颊内有伤口  说明
There's a cut inside of her cheek, indicating that
她被人狠狠打了个耳光
She was slapped, hard.
但奇怪的是
But here's the weird part--
刺伤她的凶器又长又尖
She was stabbed with something long and sharp.
不是一般刀伤
It wasn't your typical blade.
怎么说
How so?
我根据伤口进行重建
Well, based on the wound,I made a reconstruction.
凶器是个四面体  顶端较细
It's 4-sided.  It's slimmer at the tip
越接近底部越粗
And gets progressively wider at the base.
我还在伤口上找到玻璃
Also, I found traces of glass in the wound.
她是被人用华盛顿纪念碑刺了吗
She was stabbed with the washington monument?
抱歉
Excuse me.
埃斯波西托  查到什么吗
Esposito, any luck?
是的  天台
Yep, rooftop
就在死者公寓的马路对面
Is right across the street from the vic's apartment.
-容易接近死者  -有线索吗
- Easy access. - You find anything?
很多烟头和汽水罐  还有一个
Lots of cigarette butts, Soda cans and an empty package
装数码相机记忆卡的空盒子
For a digital camera memory card.
送去犯罪现场部门  看能否提取指纹
Get it to c.s.u. See if you can pull any prints.
现在就去
On our way.
-还有什么吗  -是的
- Anything else? - Yeah.
初步毒素检查显示  死者血液酒精浓度为点02
Preliminary tox screen indicates her blood alcohol was .02.
而且体内有少量艾德美存在
And there were traces of Addmair  in her system.
-那是什么  -是一种安非他命
- What's that? - It's a form of speed
治疗患多动症的人群
Usually prescribed to people with a.d.d.
但有模特会在街头购买
But models have been known to buy it off the street
用来减肥
And use it for weight loss.
再也不能说她反对吸毒了
So much for her being antidrug.
我猜不只是工作和跟踪狂
I guess the job and the stalker
让她紧张
Weren't the only things making her tense.
你不觉得有人跟踪詹娜很奇怪吗
Do you find it odd Jenna had a stalker?
不  为什么
No, not really. Why?
她不是超模海蒂·克拉姆
Well, she wasn't heidi klum.
她的广告大片都还没出来
She hadn't even had a national campaign.
或许那家伙认为
Well, maybe the guy figured
他得提前做好准备
He was getting in on the ground floor
聪明的跟踪者
Stalker-wise, you know?
最早的
Beat the rush.
你就是忍不住  是吗
You couldn't resist, could you?
写的不错吧
Pretty nice write-up, Huh?
如果你喜欢这些花边新闻
Yeah, if you like those sorts of fluff pieces.
花边新闻  这记者把你写成了
Fluff? The reporter made you sound like you're
夏洛克·福尔摩斯和
A cross between Sherlock Holmes
安吉丽娜·朱莉的混合体
And Angelina Jolie.
这照片也很不错
And the picture isn't half bad either.
虽然你不常需要交叉双臂
Though you don't always need to cross your arms.
没关系
It's fine.
那你为什么不开心
Then why are you upset?
我没不开心
I'm not upset.
-你看上去不开心  -不  我没有
- You look upset. - Well, I'm not.
-那如果不开心  会告诉我吗  -我没有
- But if you were upset, you would tell me, right? - I'm not.
-但如果有  -这不重要  因为我很好
- But if you were - It doesn't matter because I'm not upset.
理查德·卡塞尔  风云人物
Richard Castle-- The man of the hour.
你是说这个吗  很拉风吧
Oh, do you mean this? Pretty flattering, right?
-至少我这么认为  -过时了 朋友
- At least I thought so. - Old news, my friend.
我说的是昨天  时装周
I'm talking about yesterday, Fashion week.
有消息说  你得到了一点纪念品
Word on the street is you brought back a little souvenir.
莉娜小甜心的电话号码
The digits of a particular Young honey named Rina?
莉娜
Rina.
我可能有和他们提过
I might have mentioned it to them in passing.
卡塞尔
Come on, Castle.
同情下你的兄弟们  没遇过多少模特
Take pity on your model-deprived brothers.
给我们点资料  她是性感曲线分明型
Give us the stats. Was she the sexy, curvy lingerie type
你可以
That you could just--
或是  小麦肤色身材健美的比基尼型
Or the--the toned and tanned Bikini-wearing type?
她是那种  我好开心
She's more like The "I'm totally psyched
刚拿到驾照型
I just got my driver's license" type.
你们俩得改改了  因为你们
You two so need to evolve, because that little girl
谈论的那个小女孩
You're talking about Like a piece of meat,
那是别人的女儿  知道吗
That's somebody's daughter, All right?
她是某人的保姆
She's somebody's... Babysitter.
犯罪现场部门找到了记忆卡盒子上的指纹
You guys, c.s.u. Matched a print Off the memory card packaging.
威尔·詹姆士  魅力男孩
Will James. Uh-huh. Real charm boy.
家庭暴力背叛缓刑
On probation for domestic assault,
-还有好几个限制令  -看来是他了
- Couple of restraining orders. - Sounds like our guy.
威尔·詹姆士  纽约警局
Will James, nypd!
没人
We're all clear.
这里也没有
Yeah, clear in here, too.
看我发现了什么
You guys, look what I found.
-詹娜的档案照片  -档案照片
- Jenna's comp card. - Comp card?
公司用来给模特找工作的
Yeah, agencies use it to get models work.
就一张照片  不太像跟踪狂
A single comp card? That's not very stalkery.
怎么没有满墙詹娜的照片
Where's the big creepy wall of Jenna?
-贝克特  -什么事
- Beckett? - Yeah.
有线索  长焦镜头相机
I think I got something-- A camera with a telephoto lens.
拍了些什么
What has it got on it?
没东西  可能被删掉了
Nothing. Maybe it's been erased.
旗盈科技  4G储存卡
Ah. Q-tech, 4 gig.
对得上天台找到的盒子
Same as the empty package on the roof.
交给犯罪现场部门  看能否恢复里面的照片
Get it to C.S.U. See if they can recover the photos.
如果这家伙真的迷恋詹娜
If this guy had a thing for Jenna,
那他还真表现得不太明显
He sure was subtle about it.
知道什么是名片照吗
Did you know What a comp card is?
我也不知道
Yeah, me neither.
警官  我能帮什么忙吗
Can I help you, officers?
威尔·詹姆士吗  举起手来
Will James? Get your hands up.
我们有证据证明你曾到过她家对面的天台
We can place you on the rooftop of the building across from hers,
如果你不是去偷拍她  那你在那里干什么
So if you weren't taking photos, what were you doing there?
我没有杀她
I didn't kill her, all right?
星期天我根本不在这里  我去上班了
I wasn't even here sunday.  I was workin'.
你说过了  在亚特兰大的赌场
Right, at the Casino over in Atlantic city.
别担心  我们会查清楚的
Don't worry. We're running it down now.
与此同时  希望你能解释
In the meantime, maybe you can explain
为什么这个会出现在你家里
How this got in your apartment.
有漂亮妞的照片不犯法吧
Having pictures of hot chicks is not a crime.
没错  但给她写恐吓信就犯法了
No, but sending them threatening letters is.
请允许我念一下  今天你的妆太浓了
If I may... "You were wearing a lot of makeup today.
让你看起来像个荡妇
It made you look like a slut."
你们认为是我写的吗
Oh, you guys think I wrote that?
这家伙可真老练
That guy is aptly named.
他让我神经紧张
He gives me the willies.
我们遇到问题了
We have a problem.
他的不在场证明是真的
His alibi checks out.
你在跟我开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
和赌场经理确认过了
Talked to the manager at the casino where he works.
他说案发当晚威尔·詹姆士一直在那里
Says that Will James was there the night the girl was killed.
一定是哪里出了错
There's gotta be some kind of mistake.
可能他和老板关系不错  在帮他撒谎
Maybe his boss is in on it, covering for his friend.
我也这么想
I thought so.
所以看了他们送来的监控录像
So they sent over the security footage.
詹姆士一整晚都在代客停车
James was parking cars all night.
他不是凶手
He's not our guy.
好吧  我不太明白
Okay, I don't... I don't understand.
我们可以起诉他跟踪罪
We're holding him on stalking charges.
但他并没有杀害你妻子
But he didn't kill her.
但是他写了那些信  拍了那些照片啊
He sent those letters, right? He took the pictures?
在犯罪现场部门恢复储存卡里的照片之前
We won't know for sure unless C.S.U.
我们还无法确定都是他干的
Is able to recover files from the camera card.
不管是谁  我们都会将他绳之以法
Whoever killed Jenna, we will find them.
我保证
I promise.
好的  我会尽力协助你们
Okay. Just-- Whatever I can do.
有件事我们想要弄清楚
Well, there is something that we're trying to figure out.
法医在詹娜血液中检测出艾德美
The medical examiner said that she found Addmair  In Jenna' s blood stream.
是一种安非他命
It's a type of amphetamine.
不不  詹娜从不吸毒
No. No. Jenna didn't use drugs.
但有人说她最近常常精神紧张  异常急躁
Some people say that she'd been Acting nervous lately, edgy.
没错  那是因为她压力太大
Sure. That was the stress.
那些恐吓信把她吓坏了
Look, these letters, they really scared her.
她又不想告诉她的同事这些事
She didn't want to tell people at work about 'em.
最近她的工作怎么样
How were things going for her at work?
有没有跟什么人有摩擦
Was there anyone she didn't get along with--
法罗先生对她怎么样
Mr. Farrow perhaps?
不  她很喜欢泰迪
No. Look, she loved Teddy.
她和所有人都相处得很好
She got along good With everyone.
我不知道  可能是有一个人
I don't know. Maybe this one guy.
是个摄影师  他们吵过架
A photographer. They had a fight.
为什么
About what?
是那家伙负责替法罗的新一季产品拍照
I guess he was the guy that was gonna shoot The Farrow campaign.
所以他和詹娜上周试拍了一次
So last week, he and Jenna, they did this test shoot.
她回家以后哭得很伤心
She came home crying,
说是她的照片拍得很糟
Said that Her pictures were awful.
她很担心保不住工作
She was worried she wouldn't get the job now.
詹娜有说怎么回事吗
Did Jenna say What went wrong?
只是说他不喜欢她
She said that he just didn't like her.
说他存心拍得不好搞破坏
He was trying to ruin it for her by making her look bad.
你知道这个摄影师的名字吗
This photographer-- Do you know his name?
门罗先生  你和詹娜之间怎么回事
Mr. Monroe, what happened Between you and Jenna?
詹娜是个好模特  人也不错
Look, Jenna was a great model and a great girl
但那天精神不太集中  表现失常
But that day, She was unfocused, awkward.
我们谈了一下  解决了矛盾
We had words, But we resolved our issues.
怎么解决的
How?
我答应她有空帮她免费试拍一次
I agreed to do another test on my time and my dime.
本该是昨天秀结束后进行的  不过
We were supposed to meet yesterdayAfter the runway show, but--
能否肯定地告诉我案发当天
Can you confirm where you were at
凌晨一点到五点  你在哪里
Between 1:00 and 5:00 a.m. The night she died?
在扎克·珀森[服装设计师]的派对上
I was at the zac posenparty
凌晨三点才离开  然后回家睡觉
Until 3:00, and then home asleep.
谢谢你  门罗先生
Thank you, Mr. Monroe.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen
泰迪·法罗
Teddy Farrow!
下午好
Good afternoon.
这一周是泰迪·法罗公司的艰难时期
It's been a hard week for us here at Teddy Farrow.
我想你们都听说了
I'm sure you've heard,
周日晚上  我们失去了一位员工
We lost one of our own on sunday night.
詹娜·麦博伊德过早地离开了这个世界
Jenna Mcboyd was taken from this world too soon.
尽管我们悼念她的离去
But even as we honor her memory,
但我想她也希望我们继续努力
She would've wanted us to carry on.
所以今天我请诸位来到这里
And that's why I've invited you here,
向你们介绍本季的新代言人
To introduce the new face of my collection.
她同样才华横溢
She's an exciting talent.
相信我们会共创辉煌
And together, we shall achieve great things.
掌声欢迎塞拉·古德温小姐
I give you Miss Sierra Goodwin.
这位塞拉小姐再次代替了好友詹娜
This Sierra' s stepping in for her good friend Jenna again.
是我看错了还是  她真的看上去很开心
Is it just me Or does she look really happy?
泰迪说新代言人什么来着
What was it that Teddy was saying about his new face?
照片会登上所有杂志和时代广场广告牌
A picture in every magazine, A billboard in times square,
还有丰厚的收入
A huge paycheck--
绝对值得为之杀人
Definitely worth killing for.
卡塞尔  你现在说的是一个女孩
Castle, you're talking about one girl
为了一份工作而谋杀另一个女孩
Murdering another for a job.
不仅是工作  是广告大片
It's not a job. It's a campaign--
简直就是黄金机会  嫉妒就是动机
A career-mer-maker--and jealousy's a classic motive.
你应该看过那种电影
You've seen the films--
《天才雷普利》《双生兄弟》  还有
"The talented Mr. Ripley," "Dead ringers," and, of course,
被低估的经典《美国舞娘》
The underrated classic  "showgirls."
《美国舞娘》里可没有死人
Nobody murdered anyone  In "showgirls."
我懂了
I hear.
塞拉想要成为泰迪的宠儿
Sierra wants to be Teddy' s favorite.
但她总是屈居第二
But she's always second choice.
于是塞拉想  要是詹娜消失呢
Sierra thinks, What if Jenna was gone?
那么我就成了首选
Then I'd be number one.
那我就能得到想要的一切
Then I would finally get Everything that I deserve.
是夜  她知道机会来了
And then one night, She sees her chance.
她把詹娜引到一处安静的地方
She lures Jenna somewhere quiet...
四处无人
Deserted.
当詹娜转过身去的刹那  塞拉捅了她
And when Jenna turns her back, Sierra stabs her.
用她包里的华盛顿纪念碑吗
With the statue of the washington monument that she carries in her purse?
然后偷走了她的鞋子
And then steals her shoes.
推理不太严密  但既然来了
Not a perfect theory, But we're here anyway.
多了解一点塞拉·古德温的情况也无妨
So no harm in learning a little bit more About what makes Sierra Goodwin tick.
我看到能挖线索的人了
And I see just the girl to clue us in.
里克
Rick.
您应该称呼我卡塞尔先生
Uh, that's Mr. Castle to you,
莉娜小姐  这位是贝克特探长
Missy Rina, This is detective Beckett.
贝克特探长  这是莉娜  曾是我的保姆
Detective Beckett, rina. She used to babysit for me.
我是说  照顾阿丽克西斯
For--I mean Alexis.
你挺会保密啊
You don't say?
事实上  我们是为了詹娜的事来的
Actually, we're here About Jenna.
那件事太可怕了
Oh. That was so terrible.
对  她和塞拉·古德温真的是闺中密友吗
Yeah. Was it true that she and Sierra Goodwin were kinda b.f.f.s?
不能说是闺中密友
I wouldn't say b.f.f.s.
塞拉既是朋友也是对手
Sierra' s more of a frenemy.
-怎么说  -她跟大家都相处得不好
- How so? - She doesn't play well with others.
她把别人推下过楼梯吗
She ever push anybody down the stairs?
那倒没有  不过干过些蠢事
No. Stupid stuff, really--
故意说错试镜时间
Lying about when a call time is,
在你的内衣里涂上痒痒粉
Itching powder  In your underwear--
等等  还有一次
Wait, and this one time,
她把一粒减肥药碾碎
She crushed up a diet pill
放进另一个模特的香槟里
And dropped it into another model's champagne
你是说她给别人投药
You're saying she dosed someone.
那个女孩疯了
The girl got all wired
还当面骂凯文·克莱是个无聊的老混蛋
And called Calvin  Klein a boring, old fart.To his face..
谢谢你  莉娜  谢谢你的帮忙
Thank you, rina. You've been very helpful.
想和我分享一下你的想法吗
Got something you want to share with the class?
我在想
I was just thinking...
有可能詹娜根本没有吸毒
Maybe Jenna didn't use drugs.
可能是塞拉在她的饮料里下了药
Maybe Sierra was slipping 'em  Into her drinks
让她在泰迪·法罗面前表现得疯癫失常
When Teddy Farrow was around to make her seem crazy or paranoid.
接下来就到了令人发指的罪行了
Now that is an evil deed
简直就是《美国舞娘》的特别版情节
Worthy of the "showgirls" Special edition.
他们俩来这里干什么
What are those two doing here?
伙计们  有什么发现
Okay, guys, What's going on?
技术部恢复了威尔·詹姆士储存卡的照片
Tech managed to recover E deleted photos from Will James' memory card.
他可能不是杀害詹娜的凶手
He might not have been Jenna' s killer,
但他肯定就是那个跟踪她的人
But he was definitely her stalker.
你们大老远开车来就为了这事
And you drove all the way Down here just to show me this?
我们以为你现在就想看
We thought you'd want 'em right away.
你们真是想得太周到了
That is so thoughtful of you guys.
贝克特  你觉得怎么样
What do you think, Beckett?
-怀念从前的光鲜生活吗  -什么生活
- You missing the glamorous life? - The what life?
卡塞尔  那位美女在这里吗
Castle, hey, is your, uh, your girl here?
莉娜
Rina.
莉娜曾是阿丽克西斯的保姆
Rina used to babysit Alexis, Fellas.
所以在大人物里克的眼里
So as far as big Rick here is concerned,
她现在可是碰不得
She might as well be wearing a chastity belt.
感谢你栩栩如生的陈述
Thank you for that visual image.
还要谢谢你称我为  大人物里克
Thanks. And also, thank you for calling me "big Rick. "
还有  我们该和威尔的女朋友谈谈
Hey, by the way, our buddy will Has a girlfriend We might want to talk to.
这后面还有几张她的照片
There's, uh, some photos Of her right here in the back.
是裸照
Mm. Naked photos.
卡塞尔  快看
Castle, check this out.
看裸照吗  如果你坚持的话
Look at naked pictures?  If you insist.
她怎么是威尔·詹姆士的女朋友
She's will James' girlfriend?
看来除了泰迪·法罗
Looks like Teddy Farrow
塞拉还为别人当模特
Isn't the only guy that Sierra modeling for.
你们把场面搞成那样  知道意味着什么吗
Have you any idea of the spectacle you just caused?
为什么要从我的发布会上
I mean, why the hell would you drag the face of my campaign
把我的广告女主角带到这里来
Out of my launch party and bring her down here
-搞得像她是杀人犯  -因为她确实是
- As if she were some sort of criminal? - Because she is.
这是威尔·詹姆士的口供
Will James' confession.
他供认是塞拉雇他
He admits Sierra hired him
去跟踪偷拍詹娜
To take the stalker photos of Jenna.
他甚至还帮她写了那些信
He even helped her write the letters.
他还承认曾提供艾德美给塞拉
And he claims he was supplying sierra with Addmair.
是她给詹娜下的药
She was dosing Jenna.
她努力让詹娜在你面前疯疯癫癫
She was trying to make her seem paranoid around you.
她为什么要那样做
Why would she do that?
为了折磨那对涉世不深的夫妻
To prey on the fears of a naive couple,
让他们承受不住压力  回俄亥俄
Pressure them into moving back to ohio
这样塞拉就能取代她了
So Sierra could take her place.
法罗先生  你有没有听过一句话
Mr. Farrow, have you ever heard of the expression,
我会为了那份工作去杀人
"I would kill for that job"?
可她是我的代言人
But she was my face-- My face.
你知道这对我来说意味着什么吗
I mean, have you any idea what this will do to me,
只是丑闻而已吗
The scandal?
这会毁了整个春季系列的
It will taint the entire spring line.
法罗先生  詹娜被害
A girl is dead, Mr. Farrow.
对你来说不值一提吗
Does that mean anything to you?
可那并不意味着我的事业要遭受损失
It doesn't mean my business should suffer.
只是些衣服而已
They're just clothes.
只是些衣服而已  探长
"Just clothes," detective?
衣服代表着文明
Clothes are civilization.
衣服把我们和动物区别开来
Clothes are what separate us from animals.
也不尽然吧
Not always.
她是你唯一的竞争对手
She was your only competition.
你要把她赶下台
You needed her out of the way,
你自己年轻的时日也不多了
And you were running out of time.
不  不  我没有杀她
No, no. I didn't kill her.
对  你只是给她下药
Right. You just drugged her
给她寄恐吓信而已
And sent her threatening letters.
周日凌晨两点你在哪里
Where were you at 2:00 a.m. N sunday night?
塞拉  你面临一项谋杀的指控
Sierra... You are facing a murder charge.
如果你知道些什么  现在就说出来
If you have something to say, now would be the time.
-她去了怀亚特家  -那个摄影师吗
- She went to Wyatt' s place. - The photographer?
詹娜说怀亚特毁了她的试拍
Jenna wasn't just being paranoid when she said
并不是她多疑
Wyatt sabotaged her photo shoot.
-他是故意的  -为什么
- He did. - Why?
因为詹娜不肯和他上床
Because Jenna wouldn't sleep with him.
这是女孩们公开的秘密
It's like an open secret with the girls.
你提供怀亚特想要的  他给你拍精彩瞬间
You give Wyatt what he wants, he gives you great shots.
如果你不合作  他会毁了你
If you don't, he can ruin you.
他想和詹娜上床
And he wanted Jenna.
所以他就让她在保住工作和
So he was making her choose
忠诚于婚姻之间选一个  真是个好人啊
Between her career and her marriage vows? Nice guy.
她知道第二次试拍必须得成功
She knew the photos from the second test had to be great
否则就会丢掉饭碗
Or she really would lose the job.
她需要他好好拍
She needed him to do it right this
那周日发生了什么
Time. So what's happened on Sunday?
她告诉我她制定了一个计划
She told me she had a plan.
我想她是准备答应怀亚特的要求了
I figured she was gonna give Wyatt what he wanted.
我跟她说
I just told her,
这不是什么世界末日
"It's not the worst thing in the world, you know.
你或许还会觉得欲罢不能  我就是那样
You might even like it. I did."
那是我最后一次见她
That was the last time I saw her alive.
-贝克特  -什么事
- Yo, Beckett. - Yeah.
我们调查了怀亚特·门罗  没有前科
We just got the rundown on Wyatt Monroe. No priors.
但我们发现他的公寓正位于
But turns out his apartment is right next door
文艺中心旁边
To the arts center,
从客厅就能看到
And his living room overlook
詹娜遇害的喷泉
The fountain where Jenna was killed.
他就住在案发现场旁边
He lives next to the crime scene?
我们调查了他的不在场证明
We ran that alibi that he gave you.
扎克·珀森派对有人看见
Witnesses at the Zac Posen party said
他十一点半左右离开
He left around 11:30.
他跟我们说凌晨三点才离开
He told us he left at 3:00 a.m.
还有呢  我们向泰迪·法罗的员工证实
Oh, there's more. We checked with the Teddy Farrow people.
他午夜前才赶到那个派对
They said he got to their party just before midnight.
他没说实话
He lied to us.
塞拉被捕真是让我太惊讶了
I n't tell you how shocked I was when Sierra was arrested.
你们俩很熟吗
Are you two close?
不能说很熟吧
I wouldn't say close, but I did
我只是和她合作过很多次
A number of sessions with her.
原来如此
So we've heard.
这儿的视野不错
That's a really nice view.
谢谢
Thanks.
那么我能做些什么  你可以解释一下
So how can help? You could tell me why you didn't mention
为什么不提及你周日去过法罗的派对
Going to the Farrow party on sunday
大概是一时没想起来
Night. Must have slipped my mind.
那可是时装周  我参加了很多派对
It's fashion week. I go to a lot of parties.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
别管我
Oh, don't mind me.
你和詹娜在派对上有说话吗
Did you talk to Jenna at the party?
我想是的  不过只是打了个招呼
I think I did, but just to say hello.
-你没想约她之后来你家吗  -没有
- You didn't plan on a rendezvous later on at your place? - No.
是吗  那么这些又是什么
Oh, really? Then whose are these?
克里斯提·鲁布托的桃色缎面红底鞋
Christian louboutin pink satin pumps
是泰迪·法罗借给她的
On loan from Teddy Farrow.
我不知道这是谁的
I don't know who those belong to.
-门罗先生  这是什么奖  -是希洛奖
- What is this award, Mr. Monroe?  - It's the hilo.
卓越摄影师
"For excellence in editorial photography."
貌似少了一个
Looks like one of these is missing.
门罗先生  这个奖杯在哪里
Mr. Monroe, where is it?
上周  清洁工把它摔地上了
The cleaning woman, uh, dropped it... Last week.
摔碎了
It broke.
这和那个华盛顿纪念碑倒挺像
You know, it looks just like the washington monument.
是这样吗
It does, doesn't it?
好吧
Okay.
詹娜星期天晚上是去过我家
Look. Jenna was at my place on sunday night.
但她走的时候还好好的
But she was alive when she left.
她为什么要去你家
Why was she there?
她在泰迪的派对上遇到我
She found me at Teddy's party,
说她改主意了
Said she had a change of heart,
提议我们俩从现在开始合作
Wanted us to work together from now on as a team.
而你就以为她在暗示你上她
And you assumed that was code for "do me."
我们约定在我家见面
We agreed to meet back at my place.
她如约前来  我们喝了点东西
She came in, we had a drink,
在沙发上挺舒服的
Got comfortable on the couch.
我想要直奔主题
I was ready to get down to business,
可她却想要谈论我们的交易
But she kept wanting to talk about our deal.
她是这样说的
That's what she called it.
她要我告诉她  到底具体要她做什么
Said she wanted me to tell her exactly what she had to do
才能给她好好拍
To get good shots-- Exactly.
她想让你自己说出来作为证据
She was trying to get you to incriminate yourself.
这女孩不去做间谍太可惜了
A master spy this girl was not.
我抢过她的钱包  翻出手机
I grabbed her purse, pulled out her phone.
那该死的东西摁个钮就可以录音
Damnhing had an app on it that turned it into a recorder.
她完整地录下了我们的对话
She taped our whole conversation.
她想录下他要求潜规则的录音
She wanted to record him Demanding sex for good shots
然后让泰迪·法罗听听
So she could play it for Teddy Farrow.
她又夺回手机  我们扭打起来
She grabbed the phone back. We struggled.
她抓过架子上的奖杯
She picked up my award off the shelf,
疯狂地到处挥舞
Started waving it around and acting crazy.
奖杯撞在书架上  杯顶碰碎了
She smacked thhilo into a bookshelf. The tip broke off.
我试图抢过来  却被碎片割伤了
I tried to grab it. She cut me with the edge.
所以我放弃了  她就离开了
So I backed off, and she left.
故事很精彩  可我不信
You know, that's a great story, but I don't believe you.
你们听听她的手机录音
Just listen to the recording on her phone.
我说的是实话
I'm telling you the truth.
她的包不见了
Her purse was never found.
看来能够证明你清白的证据
So it looks like the evidce that'll clear you
已经和你的希洛奖杯一起
Is lying in a landfill somewhere
被丢到某个垃圾场了
Along with your hilo.
真是倒霉透顶
Tough break.
模特行业以前可是光环四射
You know that modeling was glamourous.
这个行业也不是所有人都追名逐利
Not everybody in that business is predatory.
可看上去是那样的
It sure seem that way
詹娜最好的朋友给她下药
Jenna's best friend was drugging her,
她的摄影师谋杀了她
And her photographer killed her.
和她的死比起来  设计师更关心的
Even her clothing designer seemed more interested
却是时装秀
In his show than in her murder.
不过至少我们还是抓住了凶手  已经很好了
But at least we got the bad guy. That's something.
怎么了
What?
如果是怀亚特杀了她
If Wyatt killed her,
他为什么不把家里打扫干净
Why didn't he do a better job of cleaning up his place?
还有  为什么要把她的尸体
And why would he leave her body
就放在他的公寓门外
Right outside of his apartment?
或许他脑子不那么灵光
Maybe he's not that bright.
抑或是他确实说了实话
Or maybe he was telling the truth.
说不定不是他干的
Maybe he didn't do it.
昨日回忆那部戏怎么样了
What's up with the stroll down memory Lane?
我打过电话给经纪人
Oh, I called my agent
告诉他不接这部戏了
And told him to pass on the play.
我说  玛莎·罗杰斯不能在第一幕就死去
I said, "martha Rodgers does not die in the first act,
更不可能死在台下
And she never dies offstage."
感觉好点了吗
Feel better?
没有  感觉我已经老了
No, I feel rotten and old.
感觉我已经走到了舞台生涯的尽头
I feel like I'm dying offstage.
我也曾天真无邪  扮演主角  是大明星
I was always the ingenue, the lead, the star.
我喜欢那样
I liked it that way.
儿子  青春美丽  才华洋溢
It's a powerful thing, kiddo,
有种奇妙的魔力
To be young, beautiful, talented.
是女人都不愿放弃
No woman wants to give it up.
您依然美丽动人  依然才华洋溢
You are still beautiful and you are still talented.
你并没有失去青春
And you didn't give up your youth.
只是用它换来了睿智
You traded it for wisdom.
睿智
Wisdom.
还我青春
Gimme that.
莉娜  今晚的约会有效
Rina, yeah we're still on for the date tonight.
好的  你记得我住哪里吗
All right. You remember where I live?
待会见
I'll see you then.
什么
What?
阿丽克西斯都告诉我了
Alexis told me all about it.
这女孩对你来说太小了
At girl is too young for you.
或者我该这样说  你跟她比太老
Or I should say, you are too old for her.
不是你想的那样
It is not what you think.
失业的女艺人  免费住在玻璃房
And unemployed divas who live in glass houses rent free
就别说别人了
Should not throw stones.
说的也对
Point taken.
有什么好消息吗
What's the good word?
阳光电子
Sunshine electronics.
-那是两个词了  -不是
- That's two words. - Nope.
詹娜·麦博伊德在阳光电子买的新手机
That's where Jenna Mcboyd bought her new cell phone.
-什么  -昨晚我找她丈夫谈话
- What? - So I was talking to her husband last night,
我突发奇想  问了点她手机的事
And on a hunch, I ask him about her cell phone.
他说她那款手机没有录音功能
He said it wouldn't accommodate a recording app.
然后我查了她的信用卡账单
So I checked into her credit card receipts.
她遇害当天买了个新手机
She bought a new cell phone the day she died,
还装有全球定位系统
And it had gps in it,
她很有预见性  早就打开了
Which she had the foresight to switch on.
这么说你找到手机了
Whoa. You found it?
在西区81街的一个垃圾桶里
In a dumpster on west 81st.
有同事正送来
Uniforms are bringing it in now.
-怀亚特  住手  -把手机给我
- Stop it, Wyatt! - Give me the phone!
至此  一切正如他所说
So far it's happening just like he said it did. Mm-hmm.
这是他说的  她抢过凶器的时候
This is when he said she grabbed the weapon.
把它给我
Give that to me!
离我远点
Stay away from me.
小心点那个东西
Be careful with that thing.
他妈的
Damn it.
我流血了  你这个疯婊子
I'm bleeding, you crazy bitch.
听起来她是活着离开了那里
Sounds like she left the place alive.
但也不代表他没有追出去
Doesn't mean he didn't go after her.
但是如果他想杀她
Yeah, but if he was Gonna kill her,
就不会让她活着离开他的公寓
He wouldn't t her leave the apartment.
还在录音呢
Shh. It's still going.
我得叫辆车  我得离开这里
I need a cab.I've gotta get outta here.
我的天哪  你跟踪我
Oh, my god! Did you follow me?
等等  放开我  住手
Wait. Let go of me. Stop!
那么  我们现在怎么办
So... What's our plan?
让他认罪
Make him confess.
我觉得他不会老实招供的
I don't think he's gonna crack that easy.
如果他发现
I mean, what if he figures out
我们只是有这么一部分录音
We only have a partial recording,
而且在凶案发生之前手机内存就满了
That the memory on the phone ran out before the actual murder took place?
他不会发现的
He won't.
我们没有证据证明他是凶手
We, uh, we don't have any proof that he did it.
要是他死不承认保持沉默怎么办
I mean, what if he shuts down and doesn't talk?
他会说的
He won't.
他可不蠢  他会找一个律师的
He's not a stupid man. He might ask for a lawyer.
他会招供的  这事我来处理
He won't. Look, let me handle this.
你想进去的话可以  但是不要说话
You can go in if you want, but don't speak.
-我只是  -不要说话
- I just-- Don't speak.
你为什么跟踪我
Why did you follow me?
我的理由似乎很充分
Well, it seems like I had a good reason.
好吧  等等  她一直在录音
Okay, wait. She was recording me?
周日晚上你跟踪她去法罗的派对
You followed her to Farrow' s party sunday night
然后又跟到门罗的公寓
And then to Monroe' s aptment.
你不明白  她就是
You don't understand. She just--
她最近一直很奇怪
She had been acting so strange lately.
然后塞拉告诉我那个摄影师
And then Sierra tells me about this photographer--
你跟塞拉谈了怀亚特·门罗
You talked with Sierra about Wyatt Monroe?
她很担心我和詹娜
She was worried About me and Jenna,
她说  他们之间不仅是合作关系
That it wa-was more than just business between them,
他们俩有问题
That something was going on.
我一听说这件事  我
Look, o-once this was in my head, I--
我不由自主地一直想这事
I couldn't stop thinking about it.
是  我跟踪她去了派对
Yeah, I followed her to the party.
他们俩在一起
They were together.
她没有回家  却跑到他的家里去
When she didn't go home and she went his place instead,
我就知道了
I knew.
所以你一直等着
Okay, so then you waited.
她出来时  衣服乱七八糟
She came out. Her clothes were all messed up.
她的口红  被擦掉了
Her lipstick was... Rubbed off.
你骂他婊子
You called her a whore.
我对她说  她是我的妻子
I told her that she was my wife--
我的妻子
My wife.
然后她  她就开始哭
And she--she just started crying.
她  说我不明白
She... She said I didn't understand,
说我跟其他人没什么两样
That I was Just like everybody else.
特拉维斯
Travis...
如果你不告诉我事实  我没法帮你
I can't help you unless you tell me the truth.
然后你打了她一巴掌  伤了她的脸
And then you slapped her, hard enough to cut her cheek.
听着  我不是故意的  听着
Look, I didn't mean-- Look,
我只是  我没法  我看不清楚
I just--I couldn't-- I couldn't see straight.
就好像我已经不是我自己了
It's like I wasn't even myself anymore.
我非常生气  我只是
I was so mad, I just--
我根本不知道自己在做什么
I didn't even know what I was doing.
然后你就杀了她
And so you killed her.
不  没有  我没有杀她
No. No. I didn't kill her.
-是泰迪干的  -泰迪·法罗
- Teddy did. - Teddy Farrow?
总是在说泰迪
Aw, man. It was always Teddy.
泰迪这个  泰迪那个
It was Teddy this, Teddy that.
就好像  他在她耳朵里窃窃私语
Just, like, whispering in her ear.
告诉她怎么走路
You know, telling her how to Walk,
怎么说话  成为怎样的人
How to talk, who to be.
让她的脑袋里装满谎言
Just feeding her mind with lies.
我告诉你们吧  如果有人杀了她
I tell you what, if anyone did it,
一定是他
It was him.
就是你  特拉维斯  在那个广场
It was you, travis, In the plaza,
不是泰迪
Not Teddy. ..
站在喷泉旁
Standing by the fountain
回想着你为她做的一切
Thinking about all the things you'd done for her,
想着你搬到这个你讨厌的城市
About how you moved to This city that you hated
却被她这么对待
Only to be treated like this.
当时她手里有样东西  非常锋利
Now she had something  In her hands, something sharp.
是什么东西
What was it?
特拉维斯  你真想要我开始播放录音吗
Travis, do you really want me to turn that tape on?
你真想听听你说了什么  做了什么吗
Do you really want To listen to what you said and what you did?
她拿着一块残缺的玻璃
She was holding this broken glass.
让我离她远点
Told me to stay away.
所以你把它抢过来了
And so you took it from her.
事情就这么发生了
It just happened.
发生了什么
What happened?
我捅  捅了她
I s-- I stabbed her.
我从她背后捅了过去
I stabbed her in the back.
她想  她想离开我
Look, she was-- She was trying to leave me.
我  我这么爱她
I... Oh, I loved her so much.
我只是  我不能让她离开我
I just--I couldn't Let her leave me.
她没打算离开你  特拉维斯
She wasn't gonna leave you, Travis.
搞什么鬼  你在录音
What the hell? You're recording me?!
给我  怀亚特
Give it back,wyatt.
我不知道还能怎么办
I-I didn't know,what else to do.
我想要这份工作  怀亚特
I-I want the job, Wyatt.
但我很爱我丈夫  我不能这么对他
But I love my husband. I can't do this to him.
我不会这么做的  你伤到我了
I won't! You're hurting me!
我只想回家  我要回家
I just want to go home. I want to go home!
回家
Home.
她很想回家
She was trying to go home...
回到你身边
To you.
你还真冒险
That was a risky bluff--
威胁他要播一段根本不存在的录音
Threatening to play a recording we didn't even have.
我没觉得有冒险
It didn't seem like a risk to me.
他很爱他的妻子
He loved his wife very much.
他不想从她的死中解脱出来
He wouldn't want to relive her death.
那塞拉怎么办  怀亚特·门罗呢
What about Sierra? What about Wyatt me?
就这么放过他们  何谈公道
They just go free? Doesn't sound like justice.
我上午跟泰迪·法罗谈过了
Well, I spoke with Teddy Farrow this morning.
既然他知道了这二人对詹娜做过什么
Now that he understands What those two did to Jenna,
他的广告大片将会焕然一新
He's gonna launch a very different kind of campaign.
他将会在业内封杀他们俩
He's gonna get them blackballed  In the industry.
没人会再用他们
No one will hire them again.
你那是理想化的公道
Ah, you mean poetic justice.
作为一个作家
Well... As a writer,
我觉得我能接受这个
I guess I can live with that.
我希望自己也能这么觉得
I wish I could feel that way.
我希望自己能有一点  胜利感
I wish I could feel A sense of... Victory.
糟糕的一天过后  妮基 希特会怎么做
So what would Nikki Heat do after a bad day?
她会回家
She'd go home,
喝点烈酒  泡个热澡
Pour a stiff drink, run a hot bath,
读本好书
Read a good book.
太遗憾了  我没有一本好书能读
Too bad I don't have A good book to read.
我很想把《热浪》给你
Mm. I'd let you have "heat wave,"
但出版商不想让副本流出
But my publisher doesn't want any copies leaking out.
那怎么让《时尚》的记者读了
Why'd you let that "cosmo" reporter read it, then?
纯属宣传手段
Well, that's for publicity purposes.
你明白的  得让媒体先尝点甜头
You know, you want the press To have a little taste of...
等等  所以你才不高兴吗
Wait. Whoa. Is... Is that why you've been so upset,
因为我让她先看了那本书
Because I let her read it before you?
我是你的灵感
I am the inspiration.
先睹为快的应该是我  不是那个记者
I should be reading it Before a reporter does.
你怎么不直接说
Why didn't you just say so?
你怎么不直接给我
Why didn't you just give it to me?
你怎么不问我要
Why didn't you ask?
你怎么就没想到
Why didn't it occur to you?
明天我就给你
You'll have it by tomorrow.
-很好  -很好
- Good. - Good.
看起来很美  贝克特探长
Looking good, Detective Beckett.
你们是怎么
How did you guys--
我们是警察啊  打了电话给你老爸
We're detectives. Called your dad.
好吧  你们几个就乐吧
Okay. Okay. You guys have had your fun.
我只有17岁  我觉得做模特
I was 17, and I thought that... Modeling
比起做女服务生赚钱更快
Would be an easier way to make money Than waitressing.
确实
Right.
只有一个夏天  没什么大不了
It was one summer. No big deal.
如果你们告诉卡塞尔
And if you guys tell Castle about is,
我会灭了你们
I will kill you.
晚上好  亲爱的
Good evening, my dears.
您好
Hey there.
您看起来精神不错啊
You look in brighter spirits.
从今早开始  有什么变化吗
What's changed since this morning?
我推掉的那出戏
The play I passed on?
那个制作人给了我一个更好的机会
The producers came back with a better offer.
我刚在多尔切斯特签了合约
I was just at the dorchester signing my contracts.
所以你是主角了
So you got the lead?
其实没有  我还是演那个疯狂奶奶
Well, no, I still play the crazy granny.
但是你  你不用死了
But you--you don't die.
不  还是会死
No, still die.
-钱更多吗  -瞎说
- More money? - Peanuts.
那这次好在哪里
All right. So what's the better offer?
他们重写了剧本  我能死在台上
They have rewritten the script So that I die onstage.
我的死就是第一幕的结束
My death closes act one.
这比演主角还要好  真的
It's better than the lead, really.
奶奶是最出彩的角色
Granny's the bravura role.
真是戏如人生
In art as in life.
我太为你骄傲了
Oh. I'm so proud of you.
谢谢你  谢谢  宝贝
Oh, thank you. Thank you, my baby.
-有客到吗  -是的 是莉娜
- Are we expecting company? - Uh, that's Rina.
是她  你的约会对象
Oh, of course, your date.
不是我的约会对象
Not my date.
-你好  -你好
- Hi! - Hey.
准备好《歌舞青春》的播放马拉松了吗
Ready for A "high school musical" marathon?
我完全没问题
I'm so ready.
你好  莉娜
Hey, Rina.
-你好  卡塞尔先生  -快来
- Oh, hi, Mr. Castle. - Come on.
天哪  你穿这件T恤真是太可爱了
Oh, my gosh. That shirt  Is so cute on you.
对上号了  显然模特的世界里
Color me shocked, but apparently the modeling world
不只有性感的衣服和有意思的聚会
Isn't all sexy clothes and fun parties.
我突然想到  如果詹娜·麦博伊德身边
It occurred toe that if Jenna Mcboyd had someone
有人多关心她一点
Looking out for her a little bit,
她可能就不会出事了
She might still be alive today.
所以如果莉娜需要朋友
So if Rina needs a friend,
很显然她已经有了一个
She knows she's got one.
我的好儿子  心软耳根子软
Oh, my son... The big softie.
别担心  我知道你得保护自己的形象
And don't worry. I know You have an image to protect.
我会帮你保守秘密的
Your secret's safe with me.
欢迎有能力的影视爱好者加入我们字幕组
加入仅凭个人兴趣爱好 没有任何金钱实质回报